http://www.wrapables.com/pages/privacy-and-security

Account
Cart: (0)
Home
»
Privacy and Security
Privacy and Security
Log In / Log Out
Use the Log In button for faster access to "My Account", where you can:
Check or edit your wish list
Of course, logging in is required before you check out for any purchase. The system will prompt you to do so when you are ready to check out. Just click "View Cart" on the top of any page, and if you have not logged in already, you will be prompted to do so.
Use the Log Out button to make sure all your private information is wiped away before you leave the computer. This is especially important if you are using a public computer, for instance at school or at a library. Another way to make sure your private information is deleted is by closing your browser (Internet Explorer, Netscape, etc.).
Privacy and Security Policy
Wrapables does not rent, trade, loan, or sell your personal information, or any other information which may identify you, to third parties without your consent. We are committed to protecting our customers' privacy. The information we collect is used solely to process your order and to enhance your shopping experience. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage in order to help us refine the design and layout of the store.
Your Personal Information
When you place an order at our site, you provide us with your name, email address, credit card information, address, and phone number. We use this information to process your order and keep you up to date on its status. The financial information (credit card number, expiration date, billing address, etc.) that we collect from you is used for billing purposes. In addition, from time to time, we may make third party offers through our site. If you choose to accept such an offer, we will provide your contact and financial information to that third party.
In order to serve you best, credit card transactions are handled by a reputable third-party banking institution. Once the bank authorizes your credit card, we begin processing your order. The banking institution we do business with is under strict obligation to keep your personal information private.
We also work with third parties that perform various vital functions on our behalf. Such functions include shipping and delivering of packages, fulfilling orders, et cetera. These third parties will have access to personal information as required for them to carry out these functions on our behalf. They are also under strict obligation to keep your personal information private.
Wrapables may occasionally notify you via email of important changes to our web site or special offers we think you'll find valuable. You will only receive these emails when you have opted-in to receive them. For your convenience, at the end of every such email are directions on how to remove your email address from our list, should you desire to do so.
We may also use your Internet Protocol (IP) address and ISP name to help us diagnose problems with our server, and enhance administration of our web site. Your IP address may also be used to gather broad demographic information, as well as identify customer traffic patterns and site usage. This information aids us in merchandising and in refining the design and layout of the store.
Secure Servers
Our secure servers use advanced encryption and firewall technology to keep your personal information private. Our secure server layer (SSL) software completely encrypts the information you input so that it cannot be read as it travels over the Internet to our order management system. We have extremely strong security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information while it is in our control.
Cookies
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by the browser onto your computer's hard drive. There are two types of cookies, "Stored" and "Per-Session". Stored cookies are saved onto your hard drive permanently whereas session cookies are not. If our web site is left idle for over 30 minutes or if the browser is closed, the per-session cookie will be deleted as well. We use cookies to keep track of your current shopping session. Wrapables does not use cookies to store/retrieve your personal information. By default, most web browsers have both types of cookies enabled, but these settings can be altered. To place an order on our website, per-session cookies have to be enabled, but stored cookies do not.
Contests and Surveys
From time to time, we may run contests or other promotions on our site that asks for contact and demographic information. If you win, we will send your prize to the address you entered into our system, and notify you via email. We may also use your contact information to notify you about Wrapables promotions, specials and new additions to our site. If you prefer not to receive these emails, please follow the simple instructions on the bottom of the email and we will remove you from our mailing list.
Wrapables may also occasionally administer surveys at our site that request your opinions and demographic information. Here, we do not ask you for contact information and we will never contact you regarding your answers to a survey. Survey answers are strictly confidential. We only use survey data in an effort to better serve our customers. If you do not wish to participate in a survey, simply decline to participate when asked.
Statistics
Wrapables may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and other shopping information, to reputable third-party vendors or our marketing partners. These statistics will not include any information that identify you personally.
Your Consent
By using our web site, you are agreeing to allow us to collect the aforementioned information and use such information in the said manner. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Wrapables will cooperate with law enforcement agencies to identify any individual who attempts to use our services for illegal activities. We will also report any activity we believe to be unlawful, to the proper authorities. Additionally, we may release account information when we feel that such a release is necessary to enforce the terms of our user agreement, or to protect the rights, property and safety of our users, Wrapables or others. Other sites accessible through Wrapables have their own privacy policies and data collection practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. Wrapables is not responsible for the actions of third-parties.
In Closing
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, Wrapable's practices, or your business with Wrapables, please contact customer service at: service@wrapables.com
Please check back occasionally for any updates or changes to our privacy policy.
Terms of Sale
Thank you for shopping at Wrapables. By placing an order on our website, you signify your acceptance of the Terms of Sale set forth herein. Please take a moment to read through our terms thoroughly. These terms may be updated at any time; please check back occasionally for updates.
Copyrights and Trademarks
All materials appearing on Wrapables.com are the sole property of Wrapables, unless specified otherwise. Such materials protected by this copyright include, but are not exclusive to, any and all text; any and all images (including icons, logos, and other graphics); and any and all design elements of the website (including assembly and arrangement). You may use the content of Wrapables.com for no other purpose than shopping on this site, placing an order on this site, or for conducting other tasks associated directly with, and for the sole purpose of, shopping on this site or placing an order on this site. Unauthorized use of the materials appearing on Wrapables.com may violate copyright, trademark and other applicable laws and could result in criminal or civil penalties. Such unauthorized use includes, but is not exclusive to, copying, reproducing, republishing, modifying, uploading, transmitting, or distributing any of such materials without the prior written consent of Wrapables.
The "Wrapables" name and logo are trademarks of Wrapables, as are all custom graphics, icons, and logos found on Wrapables.com. All other trademarks or service marks are the property of their respective owners. The use of any Wrapables trademark without the express written consent of Wrapables is strictly prohibited.
Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability
Unless otherwise noted (such as our Outdoor Furniture Products), products sold by Wrapables are covered by our 30-day money back guarantee. Wrapables makes no representations or warranties, either express or implied, of any kind with respect to products sold on this site. Wrapables expressly disclaims all warranties, express or implied, of any kind with respect to products sold on this site, including but not limited to, merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. You agree that the sole and exclusive maximum liability to Wrapables arising from any product sold on this website shall be the price of the product ordered. In no event shall Wrapables, its officers, employees or other representatives be liable for special, indirect, consequential, or punitive damages related to products sold.
Wrapables.com and the materials therein are provided "as is". Wrapables makes no representations or warranties, either express or implied, of any kind with respect to Wrapables.com, its operations, content, information, materials or year 2000 compliance. Wrapables expressly disclaims all warranties, express or implied, of any kind with respect to the site or its use, including but not limited to merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. You agree that Wrapables, its officers, employees or other representatives shall not be liable for damages arising from the operation, content or use of Wrapables.com. You agree that this limitation of liability is comprehensive and applies to all damages of any kind, including without limitation direct, indirect, compensatory, special, incidental, punitive and consequential damages.
Typographical and Photographical Errors
Wrapables attempts to be as accurate as possible in our pricing, as well as our typographical and photographical depictions of products for sale; however, we cannot guarantee that product descriptions/specifications, pricing or any other content on Wrapables.com is accurate, complete, or current. In the event that a product is listed at an incorrect price due to typographical, informational or other error, Wrapables shall have the right, at our sole discretion, to either honor the displayed price or refuse/cancel any orders placed for that product at the incorrect price.
Order Acceptance Policy
Your submission of an order and/or receipt of an order confirmation automated or otherwise does not signify our acceptance of such order. Wrapables reserves the right to cancel any order that we deem necessary, at our sole discretion, regardless of the order status or whether you have received a confirmation of the order. We reserve the right to require additional information from you before accepting or processing any order.
Jurisdiction
Wrapables is a California corporation and you agree that any legal action brought against Wrapables shall be governed by the laws of the State of California without regard to its conflict of law principles. Additionally, you agree that any and all disagreements arising from your use of or orders placed through Wrapables.com will be adjudicated in the county of Alameda, California by an appropriate federal or state court.
ABOUT
About Us
Contact Us
Menu
Search
Your Order
My Account
Returns & Exchanges
